Dance Flick is a music, comedy, action film directed by Damien Dante Wayans.
Street dancer, Thomas Uncles is from the wrong side of the tracks, but his bond with the beautiful Megan
White might help the duo realize their dreams as they enter in the mother of all dance battles.
Megan, played by Shoshana Bush.
Thomas, played by Damon Wayans Jr..
Charity, played by Essence Atkins.
Ron, played by Chris Elliott.
Sugar Bear, played by David Alan Grier.
Baby Daddy, played by Shawn Wayans.
Dance Flick is a 2009 American musical comedy film directed by Damien Dante Wayans in his
directorial debut and written by and starring many members of the Wayans family.
The film was set for release in the United States on
February 6, 2009, and changed to May 22, 2009.
The film received mixed-to-negative reviews from critics.
The tone is lighthearted.